https://www.ryda.com.au/privacy-policy

category
AudioShop All AudioHeadphones6 productsMulti Room Speakers4 productsWireless Speakers8 productsCamerasShop All CamerasAbsolute Bargains13 productsDSLR Cameras35 productsMirrorless Cameras129 productsCompact Cameras82 productsVideo Cameras31 productsOptics377 productsInstant Cameras29 productsAction Cameras40 productsLenses511 productsCamera Accessories823 productsAction Cam Accessories137 productsCages & Mounts478 productsCases & Bags342 productsFlashes69 productsMicrophones118 productsMonitors & Displays5 productsTripods371 productsDrones4 productsCar AudioShop All Car AudioAV Multimedia61 productsCar Stereos46 productsAmplifiers71 productsSpeakers229 productsSubwoofers116 productsInstallation Acc's2017 productsParking Aids101 productsCommunicationsShop All CommunicationsUHF Handheld36 productsUHF In Car34 productsVHF Marine16 productsScanners10 productsUHF Acc's364 productsCordless PhonesShop All Cordless PhonesSingle Pack2 productsTwin Pack23 productsTriple Pack3 productsQuad Pack4 productsAdditional Handsets13 productsCorded Phones5 productsPhone Accessories1 productsDigital RadiosShop All Digital RadiosBedside Radios18 productsIn Car Radios20 productsInternet Radios1 productsLiving Room Radios26 productsPortable Radios63 productsDigital Radio Acc's5 productsHealth & FitnessShop All Health & FitnessActivity Trackers14 productsBush Walking36 productsCycling24 productsHeart Rate Monitors104 productsPedometers6 productsScales2 productsFitness Acc's182 productsGadgetsShop All GadgetsDigital Notetakers13 productsAction Camera31 productsBatteries & Rechargers26 productsCrash Cameras85 productsDrones4 productsMetal Detectors11 productsProjection Clocks2 productsRange Finders23 productsSpotting Scopes14 productsTelescopes33 productsPhone Holders23 productsAccessories226 productsGPSShop All GPSSpeed Camera Alert3 productsGPS Car27 productsGPS Handheld40 productsGPS Marine4 productsGPS Motorcycle5 productsGPS Truck16 productsGPS Trainers33 productsGPS Crash30 productsGPS Dog Tracking12 productsGPS Life Beacons12 productsGPS Mapping39 productsGPS Accessories257 productsMarineShop All MarineMarine Safety7 productsMarine Packages2 productsMarine Stereos47 productsMarine Speakers51 productsMarine Amplifiers5 productsMarine Subwoofers13 productsMarine Accessories62 productsMemory CardsShop All Memory CardsSD Memory Cards25 productsMicro SD Memory18 productsCF Express Memory4 productsXQD Memory Cards6 productsMemory Card Readers6 productsOutdoorsShop All OutdoorsHead Torches16 productsTorches70 productsLife Beacons & EPIRBS2 productsSafety6 productsSolar Power6 productsTorch Accessories28 productsSecurityShop All SecurityWiFi Monitoring14 productsDVR & Camera Kits26 productsSecurity Cameras63 productsOutdoor Cameras31 productsDoor Chimes6 productsAlarm Systems2 productsSecurity Accessories9 productsWatchesShop All WatchesKids7 productsMultisport36 productsNavigation42 productsOutdoor37 productsPremium Adventure19 productsRunning130 productsSwimming18 productsAccessories311 productsWeatherShop All WeatherWeather Stations38 productsWeather Sensors48 productsRemote Monitoring4 productsWeather Thermometers1 productsWeather Acc's35 productsWeather Software2 productsPromotions
Shop by
brand
View All Brands
Promotions
Hot offers
NEED HELP?
CHAT WITH US NOW
CONTACT US
CUSTOMER SERVICE
CHAT NOW
100% AUSTRALIAN
(All items shipped from our Sydney warehouses)
AUST WIDE SHIPPING
Shipping from $4.95 (Heavy items excl)
PRICE PROMISE
Seen it cheaper? Use our live chat!
GOOGLE TRUSTED STORE
Money Back Guarantee
Account
Home
Privacy Policy - Ryda
Privacy Policy
How is your personal information protected?
What information do we actually collect?
How do we use this information?
Do we share this information?
Do we use "cookies"?
Do we change our privacy policy?
How is your personal information protected?
The security of your personal information is extremely important to us. World wide standards now demand the highest possible security measures to be used to protect the online privacy of all internet users. At Ryda Dot Com we have partnered with GEO Trust International, a world wide recognised leader in online security to ensure all sensitive data you exchange with us is encrypted with one of the highest levels of encryption available today. Where many websites offer 128 Bit SSL encryption, we have taken this one step further by doubling the level of encryption to 256 BIT AES SSL encryption. What this really means is that all sensitive information you exchange with Ryda Dot Com is encrypted both when you send it to us and when our systems respond to you. Ryda Dot Com complies with strict best practice industry standards by meeting PCI and CISP certifications. This means in quite simple terms that your credit card information is not stored or transmitted on our computer servers. We have partnered with Paypal Australia and the National Australia Bank to ensure that your credit card information is only processed by Paypal and the NAB banking portal. We do not hold or collect your credit card information. Furthermore, we do not accept phone orders, facsimile orders or orders by mail. We are happy to assist with your order over the phone or email but we will not accept your credit details over the phone or any other means that is unsecured, NOR should you provide your credit card details to any other party if asked for.
What information do we actually collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, write a review, respond to a survey. When placing an order we will ask for your email address, postal address, phone number and credit card information. Your credit card information is only shared with Paypal Australia and the National Australia Bank, we do not collect or store your credit card information, unless you choose to do so.
How do we use this information?
In general the information we collect is used to provide you with a better shopping experience on our website by allowing us to customise the site to suit our customers needs and requests. Our customer service staff will use details pertaining to your order to assist with order tracking and processing.
Do we share this information?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include the Ryda Dot Com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information if requested to comply with Australian law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. The information provided to our advertising partners is only used to track website and product performance and it will never contain and personal identifiable customer information.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes we do use cookies. Cookies are a very small files that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables our website to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
Do we change our Privacy Policy?
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
© 2020 RydaDotCom, All rights reserved.
